export default [
  {
    mainQuestion: 'How do I move my Australia Broadband service with me?',
    mainAnswer:
      'You’re moving; no worries! The first step is to check your address on our address checker and find out if your address is nbn™ ready.',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'My new address is nbn™ ready. What do I do?',
        answer: 'That’s great! Simply follow the steps above',
      },
      {
        question: 'What if my new address is not nbn™ ready?',
        answer:
          'If your new address is not nbn™ ready, unfortunately you can’t connect with Australia Broadband at your new address. Australia Broadband only provides internet services on the nbn™ and does not provide ADSL services. <p class="separated-paragraph">If you are an existing customer, all you need to do is email us at <a href="customercare@australiabroadband.net.au">customercare@australiabroadband.net.au</a> and let us know you are moving to an address not supported by the nbn™ and the date you would like us to disconnected your Australia Broadband nbn™ service from your old address.</p> <p class="separated-paragraph"> With Australia Broadband, there are no lock-in contracts and no early termination fees, so you can disconnect your nbn™ service at any time by giving us 1 months notice.</p>',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    mainQuestion:
      'What does it cost to move my Australia Broadband service to a new address?',
    mainAnswer:
      'We don’t charge you anything to move your Australia Broadband service to a new address.',
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'Does Australia Broadband charge any relocation fees to connect nbn™ at my new address?',
        answer:
          'We don’t charge anything to move your Australia Broadband service to your new address. If a standard NBN Co installation is needed at your new address, it will also be completed at no cost to you.',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Does the NBN Co charge any connection or installation fees to connect my new address?',
        answer:
          'A small number of homes may be subject to an NBN Co <a href="https://www.australiabroadband.net.au/help/kb/what-is-an-nbn-co-non-standard-installation/">Non-Standard Installation</a> or a NBN Co <a href="https://www.australiabroadband.net.au/help/kb/what-is-the-nbn-co-new-development-charge/">New Development Charge</a> of $300. If your new address is subject to any of these NBN Co charges, we’ll let you know before the installation and get your permission before you’re charged.',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    mainQuestion:
      'If I sign up now, will my nbn™ service be activated by the time I move in?',
    mainAnswer:
      'The connection time frame will depends whether or not your new address has been connected to the nbn™ previously.',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'My new home has previously been connected to the nbn™',
        answer:
          'If your new home has been previously connected to the nbn™, we’ll normally activate your Australia Broadband nbn™ service typically within 2-5 days. This may take longer if the former tenant or owner did not disconnect their nbn™ service before you moved in.',
      },
      {
        question:
          'It is the first time my new home is connecting to the to the nbn™',
        answer:
          'If it is the first time your new home is connecting to the nbn network, we’ll arrange the first available appointment with NBN Co for an NBN Co technician to connect your nbn™ service. Typically, new nbn™ connections are completed by the NBN Co within 5-20 business days. This varies depending on your nbn™ connection type as well as the availability of the NBN Co technicians in your area. <br> <p class="separated-paragraph">We will let you know if you need an appointment after we have submited your order to the NBN Co.</p> ',
      },
      {
        question: 'Everything else',
        answer: '',
      },
      {
        answer:
          '<strong>Tell us early:</strong> If you’re able to give us a few weeks’ notice, we should be able to connect you on, or very close to, your move in date.',
      },
      {
        answer:
          '<strong>Your Australia Broadband modem:</strong> You should be able to use your existing modem at your new address but how you connect it might change.',
      },
      {
        answer:
          '<strong>NBN Co Technicians:</strong> Sometimes when an NBN Co technician attempts to connect your service they might discover that the job will require more work than expected and they may not be able to complete all the work on the day. Sometimes NBN Co technicians can’t make it to your premises on the agreed day due to weather conditions or other unforeseen events. If this happens, we’ll keep you updated as we work with the NBN Co to complete your connection.',
      },
      {
        answer:
          '<strong>NBN Co Timeframes:</strong> Please note that these are usual connection timeframes only. We may be able to get you online sooner or your order may take a little longer than anticipated. While Australia Broadband will always do its best to get you connected as soon as possible, it is the NBN Co (or its third party contractor) that performs all nbn™ connections and installations across Australia, therefore connection timeframes are determined solely by the NBN Co Ltd.',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    mainQuestion:
      'What happens to my Australia Broadband VoIP number when I move?',
    questions: [
      {
        answer:
          'When you move home you can take your <a href="https://www.australiabroadband.net.au/nbn-plans/#call-rate-info">Australia Broadband VoIP</a> number with you, if you are moving within the same state. If you relocate to another state you will need a new number.',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    mainQuestion:
      'There is already a service connected at my new address but it’s not in my name, what can I do?',
    questions: [
      {
        answer:
          'If the previous occupants have not disconnected their service, we’ll need to get <a href="https://www.australiabroadband.net.au/help/kb/i-need-to-provide-proof-of-occupancy-what-do-i-do/">some paperwork</a> from you, before the existing service can be legally disconnected. Once the paperwork’s received and verified, you should be connected within 10 business days depending the type of nbn™ connection.',
      },
    ],
  },
];
